superstock.com 2019-04-26

# SuperStock Stock Photography, Rights Managed & Royalty Free Images

## Privacy Policy

RGB Ventures LLC d/b/a SuperStock (“SuperStock”) respects your concerns about privacy and security.

**SuperStock is committed to the principles of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR):**

  * Personal data must be processed fairly and lawfully
  * Personal data must be obtained only for specified and lawful purposes
  * Personal data must be adequate, relevant and not excessive
  * Personal data must be accurate and kept up-to-date
  * Personal data must not be kept for longer than necessary
  * Personal data must be processed in accordance with the rights of data subjects
  * There must be measures against unlawful or unauthorized processing of personal data

SuperStock collects certain information about you to enable us to do business with you and improve our services. This privacy policy informs you about how we use information that identifies you personally when you use the www.superstock.com (“Site”). If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you are not permitted to access this Site.

By submitting your information to SuperStock, you agree to the practices described herein and to SuperStock’s Site term found here and the image licensing agreements on this Site. This Site, operated in the United States, and the information collected from this site may be retained indefinitely, and may be stored, accessed, and used in jurisdictions whose privacy laws may be different or less protective than those of your home jurisdiction. SuperStock may disclose this information to affiliates, subsidiaries, agents, third party content providers, and necessary payment processors, whose privacy policies and practices may be different from those of SuperStock, and for which SuperStock assumes no responsibility. Information about our customers, including personal identifying information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, sale of the SuperStock assets or acquisition as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the SuperStock. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or protect the rights, property or safety of our SuperStock, employees, customers, or the public. Other than as described above, SuperStock does not sell or rent information about its customers to third parties.

INFORMATION COLLECTED

When you visit this Site, some information may be collected automatically as part of the site's operation such as your IP and email address and navigational information. Your name, address, phone number, email address, password, and other information are collected when you register online with us. Registration enables you to access and license higher resolution images and to enter into a license to use images for comp purposes.

If you wish to license an image from us, your username, password, full name, telephone number, email address and postal address, your credit card number or other personally identifying information is collected to complete the license agreement or to receive products or services. Your email address is used to confirm the licensing transaction.

From time to time we may ask you questions relating to your user preferences in order to better serve you and improve the use of this Site. Providing information regarding your usage and preferences is always voluntary, however, if you choose not to provide the information, some products and services may not be available to you.

We may use your email address to contact you regarding our services, products and promotional offers for direct marketing purposes. If you do not wish to receive direct marketing, you may opt out by contacting us at the CONTACT US portion of this site and notifying us that you no longer wish to receive promotional information.

We collect information about your use of this Site and our customers in the aggregate about how our site is used by our customers, in order to improve our service and our Site.

We collect your orders, your use of Creative Boards and other account information as part of your sales history with us. You may review and correct your information by contacting us privacy@superstock.com.

We may disclose to carefully chosen third parties navigational and transactional information in the form of anonymous, aggregate usage statistics and demographics but only in forms that do not reveal a your identity or confidential information.

COOKIES

When you visit this Site, a text file called a cookie is placed in the browser directory of your computer's hard drive. A cookie is information that a website can store on your web browser and later retrieve. The information that cookies collect includes the date and time of your visit, your registration information and your navigational and licensing information. It allows the web browser to recognize the pages you have been to when you are visiting the site, and allows you to quickly return to viewed pages. Cookies are not linked to you as an individual and cannot be used to track where you have been either before or after you the Site. Most browsers allow you to decline cookies, but if you elect to do so, certain pages and user features such as Creative Board may not display properly. You are free to delete cookies after your session, and your browser should contain instructions on how to do this.

DATA SECURITY

Whenever you submit an order to SuperStock, you do so over a secure (i.e., encrypted) connection. This ensures that your personal information is not at risk. Additionally, we encrypt your credit card information and store it in a secure location, which can be accessed only by authorized personnel.

UPDATING OR CORRECTING INFORMATION

If at any point you wish to access your personal information to (1) change your preferences, (2) review the accuracy, or (3) correct, supplement or modify your information, you may edit your profile through the this website or make a written request to sales@superstock.com.

LINKING TO OTHER WEBSITES

Website, to which we link, including but not limited to the sites of subsidiaries and third party content providers, may have different privacy policies and practices from those disclosed here. We assume no responsibility for the policies or practices of linked sites.

MINORS

SuperStock does not intend to either solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are under 18, you should not use or enter information on this Site.

In event of a data breach

We have put measures in place to minimize the risk of a data breach, but in the event of such a data breach, we are aware of our responsibilities to notify the breach to the ICO and to affected data subjects, and we will act promptly to reduce the impact it would have on the rights of data subjects and to ensure that any necessary improvements to our data storage and handling procedures are made.

Training in data protection law

All SuperStock staff have been trained in the basic principles of data protection law and in the way in which this affects their department and activities.

Contact

Please address any enquiries to our Data Protection Officer privacy@superstock.com. They work closely with our General Manager and IT Department on data protection matters.

Updated 1 May, 2018
